I'm going to discuss about the importance of Java language. Previously we discussed
about the Java language, how to develop the Java tracking system. Today we are going to
start a new topic called Java applications, where the Java
application are used. Java applications are basically used in the banking system
which have the main database rational relational and rational schema like a
pink. We have the importance on more on the consistency and the transition
values. And next our Java application is mostly used on an AI platform to monitor
the logs, to monitor the banking system more frequently and more powerful.
Learn to talk about work in an advanced way. Instead of saying I'm good at to
talk about your skills, try saying I'm proficient in. I'm proficient in using a
range of computer software. Instead of saying I know a lot about, you could say
I have extensive experience in or with. I have extensive experience with
animals. Instead of saying I helped to, a more advanced expression is I played a
pivotal role in. I played a pivotal role in implementing the new system.
Instead of I get on well with my colleagues, you could say I have an
excellent rapport with my colleagues. Instead of saying I'm unemployed, you
could say I'm in between jobs or I'm between projects right now. Can you
think of any other alternatives? Let me know in the comments. I stopped
drinking water or I stopped to drink water. Which should I say? No, I stopped
drinking water. If I say I stopped drinking water, it means I have given up.
I don't drink water anymore. Maybe I only drink milk now. If I say I stopped
to drink water, it means I stopped what I was doing to drink water.